

NICOLA GRECO

CONTACTS



(+39 324 783 7371 niccogreek@gmail.com



github.com/Nicogreco2001

16/11/2001 - Rome, Italy

ABOUT ME

I am a 21 year old student, currently attending a bachelor's in Bioinformatics. I have a general knowledge of Biology and knowledge of Bioinformatics techniques. I am a quick learner and I consider my self a responsible and reliable person.

SKILLS

- Good knowledge of Python
- Good knowledge of PyMol
- Knowledge of R, and DeSeg2 package
- Knowledge of R Markdown for presentations

EDUCATION AND TRAINING:

09/2020 - CURRENT **BSC BIOINFORMATICS** - University of Rome "La Sapienza" - Rome, Italy

- Main courses: Bioinformatics I-II, Complex Biomolecular Networks, Al and Machine Learning
- GPA: 29.6/30

09/2015 - 07/2020 <u>HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA (100/100)</u> – Liceo scientifico statale "G.B. Morgagni" – Rome, italy

· Scientific studies (Maths, Phisics, Biology)

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Summer Schools and international experiences: 4 Summer Exchange Programs in Dublin (2019), Brighton (2017) and Cambridge (2016); School Exchange Program in Houten, Netherlands (2019)

Winner of "Fee waiver for deserving students" at University of Rome "La Sapienza": Tax exemption for having graduated with 100/100 at high school and maintaining a GPA higher than 27

WORK EXPERIENCES

02/2022 - 11/2022

COURSE ORIENTATION FOR HIGH SCHOOL STUDENTS -University of Rome "La Sapienza" - Rome, Italy

- · Holding an online information desk to help students during application procedure to BSC Bioinformatics
- Participated to the Open Day to present my Bachelor's degree

04/2020 - 05/2020 **VOLUNTEER** - Caritas - Rome, Italy

Helping homeless people during Covid-19 lockdown